Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the Socialist Party (U.S.) PE.032
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Young People's Socialist League (YPSL), 1916-2002; 295347
  - Labor Action Group: Socialist Education Project (Austin, TX), undated; 295405 (Box 12)
  - Merger: Socialist Youth League, 1950-1958; 295402 (Box 12)
  - Newark (NJ), 1935; 295406 (Box 12)
  - New England, 1926; 295411 (Box 12)
  - Pamphlets, undated; 295400 (Box 12)
  - Philadelphia, PA, undated; 295407 (Box 12)
  - Princeton Chapter, circa 1962; 295408 (Box 12)
  - San Francisco, 1911; 295409 (Box 12)
  - Socialist Song Books, undated; 295401 (Box 12)
  - Youth Committee for Thomas and Nelson, 1936; 346680 (Box 12)
- Series VI. Election Campaign Handbooks, 1908-1937; 377520
  - 1911, 377521 (Box 13)
  - 1914 (in Finnish), 377522 (Box 13)
  - 1916, 377523 (Box 13)
  - 1920, 377524 (Box 13)
  - 1932, 377525 (Box 13)
  - 1937, 377526 (Box 13)
  - Campaign Committee (Philadelphia, PA), 1908-1909; 377527 (Box 13)
  - Campaign Committee (Schenectady, NY), 1913; 377528 (Box 13)
  - Information Department, 1914; 377529 (Box 13)
  - Mason County, circa 1913; 377530 (Box 13)
  - National Campaign Committee, 1912; 377531 (Box 13)
  - National Campaign Committee, 1928; 377532 (Box 13)
  - National Headquarters, 1908; 377533 (Box 13)
  - New York State, 1930; 377534 (Box 13)
  - Socialist Municipal Campaign Committee, 1933; 377535 (Box 13)
  - Washington State, 1916; 377536 (Box 13)